想在此处添加您的广告信息？立即联系 www.OpenSubtitles.org
Okay, I'm going to ask you
to take a deep breath in.
深呼吸
And you can let it go.
呼气
Should I do it again?
再继续吸气吗
No, one is good.
不用 一次就够了
...upset about?
Apparently last tuesday...
知道为什么生气吗 上个星期二
...we had this fundraiser...
有个筹款人带的是棒棒糖蛋糕
...and I brought cupcakes,
she brought cake pops.
而我带的是纸杯蛋糕
And she's like,
"That's too similar."
她的意思好像是干吗跟我带一样的
I'm like,
"No, a cupcake is a cupcake.
我说 哪里 纸杯蛋糕就是纸杯蛋糕
A cake pop is cake
with a stick in it."
棒棒糖蛋糕是有跟棍子插住的
Cynthia? I'm going to ask you
to scooch down the table now...
辛西娅 你要挪一下
Mmm-hmm....and turn over, please.
再翻下身
We are grown women and we're
fighting about cake pops.
我们都是成年人了 还在为蛋糕争个你死我活的
You know I mean let's get over it already!
But the real issue is...
这也没什么好说的 不过问题是
...her daughter Alicia
is a very nice girl,
她女儿艾丽西亚是个好孩子
but not very smart,
whereas my daughter Anna...
虽然不聪明 可是我的女儿安娜
Hey, Eva.
Nice to see you.
伊娃 你好啊 见到你真好
Hey. Come on up.
上来吧
- How's everything? - Great.
- Alright.
-还好吗 -不错 -那就好
Excuse me.
让一下
Hey, Mom.
Where are you going?
你去哪
To a party with Sarah and Will,
陪莎拉和威尔去个派对
so they don't have to be alone.
他们就不会无聊了
You wanna come?
你想去吗
Why?
为什么
Because you're leaving soon,
and I want to be with you.
因为你快走了 我想陪你啊
I'm good, thanks.
我很好 谢谢
- Have fun. - Thanks, honey.
-玩的开心 -谢谢 亲爱的
She's driving us totally crazy.
我们快疯了
We can't find anything.
东西永远不知道在哪
She puts things in
the weirdest places.
她都放在乱七八糟的地方
Like, if I leave my
bracelet in the kitchen,
我放在厨房的手镯
she'll put it in a kitchen drawer!
她就会帮我扔到柜子里去
Why can't you just do it?
你为什么不能狠点心呢
I always do it. I fired the gardener.
It's not fair.
哪里没有 我炒了园丁 你这么说太不公平了
We want to fire her,
and he won't do it.
我想要炒了她 他不愿意
It's not hard for you. Why
does it have to be fair?
对你来说轻而易举 干吗要求公平
You should do it because
it's hard for you.
你觉得难为情你就去做
Oh, please.
别扯了
Come on, Sarah. You're a grownup.
You can fire a maid.
莎拉 你是个成年人了 我看好你
That's the definition of maturity?
成熟对你来说
Being able to fire your friggin' maid?
就是炒了你那该死的仆人咯
Sarah, is this
color good on me?
莎拉 这颜色怎么样
You look good. You look pretty.
很好 很配你
That's good. That's a nice look.
很好看
Whose party is this, anyway?
话说谁举办的这个派对
He's a book editor and she's an interior
designer. They know everybody.
他是个编辑 她是室内设计师 他们人缘很好
- Maybe some single men are here. - No.
-也许有黄金单身汉哦 -做梦吧
Oh, shit, I see a patient.
糟糕 有个病号
- Oh, what you gonna do?
- Will you show me?
-你想干吗 -指给我看看
- No way. - Will you show me which one is it.
-别想了 -给我看看是哪个
- Come on, introduce me.
- Stop looking. No.
-给我介绍介绍 -不 别看了
God, you're such
a wet blanket.
天啊 你太扫兴了
Oh, look it! There's that
lady from my gym. What is...
我的客户在那 太巧了
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
-再见 -拜拜
What is her name?
我忘了她名字
Oh, it's Hilary.
想起来了 希拉里
Hilary? Hilary!
希拉里 你好啊
Eva! Hi.
伊娃 好啊
It's so weird to see you here.
你怎么会在这
Eva, this is Marianne. Marianne, Eva.
伊娃 她是玛丽安妮 玛丽安妮 她叫伊娃
- Hello - How are you? - I'm good.
- Nice to meet you.
-你好 -你好吗 -很好 -很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我也是
Eva is an incredible,
incredible masseuse.
伊娃的按摩技术太棒了
- Wonderful. - Thank you very much.
-太好了 -谢谢
Excuse me a second.
I have, I have to find a bathroom.
我不行了 我得去找个厕所
That was abrupt.
她太唐突了
Oh, my goodness! Look at
those shoes and that outfit.
天啊 看看你的鞋子和衣服
You got the purse and everything?
It looks so nice.
还有包包 简直绝配啊
Thank you. I should
bring you everywhere.
谢谢 我带你逛逛吧
- I love your outfit, too. - Oh.
-你的衣服也很好看啊 -谢谢
So you're a masseuse?
你是按摩师吗
I am, yeah.
是的
Yeah?
哦
And what is it you do?
你做什么的
I'm a poet.
我是个诗人
Oh. And I'm a dreamer.
我也是啊(Poet也有空想家的意思)
No, really.
我说真的
You're really a poet?
你真的是诗人啊
I am.
对啊
You do it for a living?
用来谋生吗
- I do. - Wow!
-是啊 -太不可思议了
You do, I don't. You're
a poet, now I know it.
你用来赚钱 我用来空想 你是个诗人 我懂了
Good one.
很好
Feel free to steal it.
想要点子找我啊
Can I give that to you?
Thank you.
能帮我拿着吗 谢谢
Guess what?
猜猜怎么了
- What? - I think I just
got a new client.
-怎么了 -我搞到一个新客户
Yeah? Where?
在哪
Ah, right there.
那边
She looks clean.
她看起来不错
She's really nice and funny,
she's got great taste.
她很幽默风趣 品味不错
And very attractive.
很迷人
You probably think all the
women here are attractive.
你觉得这里的女人都很迷人吧
Pretty much.
差不多
Hold this. There's not one man
at this party I'm attracted to.
帮我拿着 这里没一个能入我法眼的
Will.
威尔
Hey! Jason! How you doing?
詹森 你好
- This is Albert. - Hi.
-这是艾伯特 -你好
- How's it going?
- How are you? Hi.
-你好 -你好
So, this is a nice party. Got all
the nice white balls hanging down.
那么多白色灯泡点缀的派对太棒了
Eva was just telling
me that there are
伊娃刚刚说这里没有
no men at the party
she's attracted to.
一个男人她看得上的
Okay.
好吧
I don't know why you would
make that announcement, but...
我不明白你干吗要说出来 但是
Really? Is that unusual?
真的吗 以前没有过吗
No, actually, it's not unusual.
No offense.
不 无意冒犯 实际上我一直这样认为
No, that's okay. There's no one
here I'm attracted to, either.
不会 我也是这样觉得的
Yeah, it's kind of
an ugly crowd, really.
人还挺多
Jason, you have a kid
in college, right?
詹森 你有个小孩在读大学 对吗
Two. Yeah.
两个
I have one
leaving in the fall.
我的小孩秋天就去上大学了
I do, too!
我的也是
- That's all I have. - Me, too.
-舍不得啊 -我也是
Come on. Your kids are supposed
to go away. That's healthy.
你们应该让他们出去闯闯 这样对他们比较好
No. Shut up.
不要 闭嘴
Yeah, shut up.
闭嘴吧
- Do the guys get boners? - No.
-没有人会有反应吗 -不会
- Oh god. Haven't we been over this? - Yes.
-天啊 你还有完没完 -对啊
I get so nervous with massages.
一想到按摩我就紧张
I'm always afraid that I'm
going to get a boner.
一直担心我会勃起
- You are?
- Absolutely. Absolutely.
-你会吗 -绝对啊
Do they hit on you?
他们会挑逗你吗
Okay, you're starting to depress me.
你让我恶心了
No, they don't hit on me.
They don't get boners, either.
不 他们不会挑逗我 也不会勃起
I do have one guy who has like a
hundred stairs going up to his house...
只是有一个人从来不帮我提按摩椅
...and he never helps me
carry my massage table.
可是上去他家有一百多个台阶
Did you ever ask him to?
你有叫他吗
- She shouldn't have to!
- No, I shouldn't have to!
-她不需要啊 -不 我不需要
Bye, guys. Thank you. Love you.
再见 谢谢 爱你们
Bye, honey!
宝贝 再见
Bye, Eva! Thanks for the ride.
伊娃 再见 谢谢你载我一程
You're welcome, Chloe.
克洛伊 不用谢
Oh, Maddy Price!
麦迪·普赖斯
You littered, honey.
别乱扔垃圾
What did you say?
你说什么
I said, pick up your trash.
You're not British.
我说把垃圾捡起来 这是美国
What a bitch.
多管闲事
- Come on in. - Thank you.
-进来吧 -谢谢
- Nice to see you.
- Nice to see you too.
-很高兴见到你 -我也是
You can just put your table
down right there.
你可以把按摩椅放这
Would you mind
taking your shoes off?
介意把你鞋子脱了吗
Oh no. Not at all.
不会啊
- Thank you. And your socks, too.
- Oh,sure? -Great. -Absolutely.
-谢谢 还有袜子也要脱掉 -真的吗 -很好 -看来要脱
Do you want some iced tea?
你喝冰茶吗
That sounds good. Thank you.
可以 谢谢
I'm so happy you called.
你打电话过来太好了
You know. Most people usually just
take my card to be polite.
因为大多数人只是出于礼貌拿了名片
Well, I'm not polite.
我可不会乱接名片喔
Oh, my, isn't this nice!
天啊 这也太好了吧
Wow.
哇
Thank you!
谢谢
Just make yourself at home, look around.
别客气 随便看看
I'm gonna go change.
I will be back in minute.
我去换衣服 马上就好
Oh god. Everything is so pretty!
Can I live here?
天哪 这也太美了吧 我能住进来吗
That tea's kind of fabulous, too.
茶也很好喝
I'm dating this guy.
He has no sense of humor.
我的男朋友太严肃了
That can be a dealbreaker.
真是大煞风景啊
I don't know what to do.
Because he's very very sweet.
我不知道该怎么办 他真的很贴心
Sweet can be good.
那很好啊
Maybe you can find someone
else to tell you jokes.
你可以和其他人讲笑话嘛
Are you married?
你结婚了吗
Divorced. Ten years.
离婚十年了
Are you still friends?
你们还是朋友吗
No, not really.
不是
We share a daughter,
but other than that...
我们除了拥有一个女儿之外
...it's hard to believe that I
ever had a laugh with that man...
难以置信的是我和他根本没共同话题
You know... let alone
create a child.
小孩也是神不知鬼不觉地怀上了
I know what you mean about your ex.
We had zero in common.
我了解 我们也是没一点共同之处
I don't know how I ever had a
real conversation with him.
我都不知道和他聊的是什么
It's crazy, right?
很疯狂 对吧
I'd like to call you pretty
soon if it's all right.
不介意的话我会马上再喊你过来的
My right shoulder is still very tight.
我的右肩还是很痛
You should ice it tonight.
晚上用冰缚着
And drink plenty of water.
多喝水
It's important to stay hydrated.
注意保持水分
Of course. Hey, do you want some chervil?
I'm drowning in it.
我会注意的 你要点雪维菜吗 我非常喜欢
Sure.
可以
I'll just give you what I've cut.
把刚摘的给你
I don't have anything to put it in, but...
没有东西给你装啊
- Oh, that's ideal. Thank you. -Alright.
-Lovely.
-我拿着就行 谢谢 -好吧 -很好
Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
What the hell is chervil? She said
she was drowning in it.
雪维菜是什么鬼东西 她说她迷上了
It's an herb.
一种药草
- A what?
- An herb.
-什么东西 -药草
How long have you known me?
我认识你也不是一天两天了
I can't understand
a damn thing you say.
我不懂你在说什么
Oh, my God.
天哪
Everything in that house was gorgeous.
I wanted everything.
每件物品都是那么完美 我想要啊
She has no cellulite!
她好瘦啊
How can that be?
怎么可能
I've never seen anything like it.
我从来没遇到过这样的
Nothing.
从来没有
Will told me some guy you met
at the party wants your number.
威尔跟我说在派对上你遇到的那个人想要你的号码
Jason's friend, I think.
应该是詹森的朋友
That's so funny. We both said we
weren't attracted to each other.
太搞笑了 我们互不来电啊
I don't know what to do.
He's kind of fat.
纠结啊 他有点肥
He is?
是吗
He's got this big belly.
他有啤酒肚
Well, you've got nothing to lose.
你又不会损失什么
No, but he does.
我是不会 他会啊
Your light Just came on.
You got a patient.
你的灯亮了 你有病人了
Better get a move on.
赶紧去吧
What happens if you never go out there?
如果你不去会发生什么
Do they like...
他们会
Sorry. Was that inappropriate?
抱歉 我是不是很无礼
Bye.
下次聊
I'm sorry about this. I swear to
God I made a dinner reservation.
不好意思啊 我保证我预订了的
No, it's okay. It's fine.
没事啊
What about you? What do you do?
跟我说说你吧 你干什么的
I work at the American
Library of Cultural History.
我在美国文化史图书馆工作
- The what? - Exactly. It's kind
of a television library.
-什么 -有点类似电视图书馆
Do you watch a lot of TV?
你经常看电视吗
No, it's television history.
不啊 我只负责放映
What's on now, I have no clue.
不过我不知道在放什么
I tried to watch one of those
Housewives of Idiot Town...
我上次看《傻瓜镇的主妇》
...but I got so depressed, I thought
I was going to jump off a building.
太难看了 我宁愿去跳楼
I know what you mean. I tried to
watch one with my daughter...
我感同身受啊 上次和我女儿一起看
...and I could not believe
what I was watching!
简直不敢相信我看到的是什么
No brains, and the fake
cheekbones and fake boobs.
脑残片 整过的颧骨和胸
Do you like fake boobs?
你喜欢隆过的胸吗
No. I like real boobs.
不 我喜欢天生的
I have real boobs.
我的没动过手术
That's working out for us then.
那很好啊
How long have you been divorced?
离婚多久了
About four years.
四年了
Was it mutual?
自愿的吗
Not really. No.
不是
Can I have her number?
能给我她的号码吗
Of course.
当然
Imagine the time that would save.
这样多省事啊
We should all put a sign on our necks
我们应该挂个牌在脖子上
with what's wrong with us. Get it all out there.
写上我们的情况 一目了然
Good idea. What would your sign say?
好主意 你会写什么
I don't know. I'm a slob. I have ear hair.
不知道 我懒的出奇 我有耳毛
There are things to get rid of that ear hair.
你可以把耳毛脱掉的啊
Researched, taken care of.
已经没了
So you're a slob, huh?
所以你很懒 对吗
Not like a dirty hoarder slob.
不过不是脏东西囤积起来的那种
What kind?
那是哪种
A normal disorganized one.
杂乱无章吧
Does your daughter live with you?
你女儿和你住吗
Half the time.
三四天吧
It aggravates her sometimes. The thing is
she and her mother are very, very neat.
有时她会忍无可忍 因为她和她妈妈都很爱干净
As a matter of fact,
their favorite store...
事实上 他们最爱逛的商店是
...I don't know,
it's... it's the store
我不记得了
with all the empty
boxes and storage.
有各种空盒子和收纳箱的商店
The Container Store?
是不是收纳箱商店（1978在美国达拉斯开张的上市的连锁商店）
Yes. The Container Store.
对 是收纳箱商店
The store that sells crap you can put
your crap in so you can buy more crap.
它卖给你一堆废物装你的一堆废物 好让你买更多的垃圾
I love that store! I love crap.
我爱那家商店 我爱垃圾
So did my ex-wife, and she puts it in
lovely, flowery and expensive boxes.
我前妻也是 她把那些废物都装进可爱华丽贵重的盒子里
You should know, they have things
in sort of manly designs there.
它们也有男性元素在里面啊
Manly designs?
男性元素
Yeah, like browns,
and little cowboy designs.
像棕皮肤的牛仔啊
Little cowboys.
牛仔啊
I mean, come on. It's hard
to live with somebody,
没有共同兴趣爱好的人
don't you think? People's habits are...
就很难相处啊 你不这样认为吗
Okay, listen to this.
I like guacamole.
好吧 我喜欢鳄梨沙拉
But I don't like the onions in
guacamole, so I take a chip...
可是我讨厌那里面的洋葱 所以我会拿块薯片
...and swirl it
around and separate
搅拌它
the onions from
the guacamole...
把洋葱拿出来
...so I can eat guacamole. Now,
that drove her bananas.
我就能吃了 她看不惯
It sounds pretty harmless.
这没什么问题啊
I thought so, but by the end of
our marriage, it made her gag.
我也这样认为 不过她还是不爽
That's not nice.
有点小题大做喔
You have...
你的手
...lovely hands.
蛮好看的
I thought, as a masseuse,
you'd have big,
我以为按摩师的手都很大
muscular hands,
but they're very lovely.
很粗糙 但是你的很好
Thank you.
谢谢
You have nice hands, too. Actually.
你的手也不错啊
Thank you.
谢谢
Kind of like paddles.
跟船桨差不多
Did they just turn
the music louder?
他们是不是把声音开大了
No, I think you just got older.
没有啊 你年纪大了
Excuse me! Do you mind turning
down the music a little?
不好意思 可以把声音关小一点吗
I'm old.
我老了
No, I'm sorry.
抱歉 不行
No, you're sorry I'm old or that
you won't turn the music down?
你对我的年纪抱歉还是调低声音
I'm not allowed to
change it, ma'am.
女士 我没有权利去调
He's so nice!
他真是友善
I find I don't like younger people.
我和年轻人代沟太大了
Eh?
什么
I'm sorry, I picked
the wrong restaurant.
不好意思 选错了餐厅
I'm having a great time.
This is delicious.
我很高兴啊 东西很好吃
I mean. I can't hear what you're saying, but...
我听不清你在说什么 不过
That's probably why you're
having a great time.
所以你才很开心吧
What is this, tomatoes?
这是西红柿吗
Tomatoes? It's watermelon.
你开玩笑吗 这是西瓜啦
That's croutons next to it.
旁边是油炸面包
Doesn't that defeat the purpose?
你故意的吗
It's nonfat yogurt, not ice cream.
You can put little stuff on it.
这是脱脂酸奶 不是冰淇淋 要加点东西上去
That looks good, man.
看起来不错
What? What?
怎么了
People tasting?
他们在试吃吗
Take a chance. Put something in your bowl.
相信你自己 直接选东西
You're not buying a house.
又不是买房子
He's happy.
他快乐就好啊
I know. Give me this.
明白 把碗给我
They have to test the flavors,
there's so many millions of them.
这么多种口味 他们都要试试
Very Berry Sorbet, and...
非常莓果冰糕
This is my daughter.
这是我女儿
Wowie kazowie! She's stunning! Lucky you.
天哪 她好漂亮 你太有福气了
She looks like her mother, thank God.
谢天谢地她像她妈妈
Here's mine.
这是我女儿
Right there.
这张
She's beautiful.
她很漂亮
You got any money?
你带钱了吗
I'm kidding.
我开玩笑呢
Oh, my God.
吓到我了
I had such a good time.
That was really fun.
今天玩得很开心
I thought so, too.
我也觉得
I'm not sure.
我还没准备好
Okay.
好的
I mean...
我想说
...I mean, maybe.
我的意思是或许
I understand.
我可以理解
It's just... I'm not sure.
就是 我也不知道
I get it. I'm not deaf.
我了解 我不聋
I'm a little deaf in...
我确实有点聋
Thank you very much.
谢谢
I like your paddles.
我喜欢摸你的手
I like your ass.
我喜欢你的臀部
My God.
天啊
Well, thank you.
谢谢
Good night.
晚安
Hi!
好啊
- Hi. - Hi.
-好 -好
How was it?
怎么样
Fine.
不错
Good. I mean, if he immediately hooks up
with someone else, I'll feel like an idiot.
我想说如果他马上另寻新欢 我就傻逼了
So don't do it.
那就不要和他上床
What are you talking about?
你们在聊什么呢
Nothing.
没什么
I can't decide if I should
sleep with Chris or not.
我不知道要不要和克里斯上床
I don't want to do
something I'll regret...
我不想后悔莫及
...but I also happen really like him,
so I don't know what to do.
但是我又很喜欢他 所以很纠结啊
And you're a virgin?
你还是处女吗
- Yeah. - Don't answer that!
-是 -别回答
Ok. Here's what I say. You can't live
in fear of making a mistake.
你不能害怕犯错误
If you want to do it, just do it.
就做就去做
- Mom. - What?
-妈妈 -干吗
Stay out of it.
别多管闲事
Ellen, honey, she just asked me.
艾伦 是她问我的
She did?
有吗
Right, Chloe? No?
克洛伊 没有吗
My bad.
我的错
Quiet.
我闭嘴
Ellen, I forgot to ask...
艾伦 我忘了问你
...what happened to Maddy Price?
麦迪·普赖斯怎么了
Oh my god. She was so rude to me the other day!
那天她太无礼了
She had a threesome with
Sage Berger and Brendon Weiss...
她和赛奇·伯杰 布伦登·韦斯搞三人行
She thinks she's Taylor Momsen.
她以为她是泰勒·莫姆森
Don't tell my mom!
别告诉我妈妈
She can tell me stuff. You never do.
她总是给我惊喜 你从来不会
Wait a minute. They had a threesome?
等等 他们3P吗
Forget it, Mom.
妈妈 别说了
What is happening?
现在都怎么了
Is everybody doing it?
现在他们都这样干吗
Mom, shut up!
妈妈 住嘴
Come out!
出来吧
You look beautiful!
你太美了
Look at you two guy.
看看你们俩
Come on!
拜托
We're not buying the same dress, Mom!
妈妈 我才不要和你买一样的裙子
We won't wear it at the same time.
我们又不会一起穿
But you look stupid.
可是你穿着不好看啊
I think I look good.
我觉得不错
You're so lumpy!
太傻了
I'd wear that if I could.
要是我能穿我也穿了
Thank you.
谢谢
No, you wouldn't.
Mom, you look crazy.
你不会穿的 妈妈 你跟疯子一样
You are not the only attractive
girl in this family, Chloe.
克洛伊 我也很迷人的啊
Why can't you dress like Ellen's mom?
She looks normal.
你为什么不能穿着像艾伦的妈妈 她多正常
So what happened with not-so-funny guy?
你和那个严肃的男人怎么样了
It didn't work out.
没下文了
- Oh. - No, it's fine. Really
-太遗憾了 -真的没事
What about you?
你呢
Do you have a boyfriend?
你有男朋友吗
I had a very good first
date over the weekend.
我们度过了一个愉快的周末
Oh, how nice! What's he like?
太好了 他怎么样
Funny.
幽默风趣
And we really never stopped talking.
我们的话题从来没听过
It was like we were old friends already.
就像我们认识很久一样
Be careful with that, 'cause
it could totally kill the chemistry.
当心这会杀火花于襁褓之中
No, no. In a good way.
不不不 是在好的一方面
Really. I mean, it was just...
it was very flirtatious.
我们只调调情
I mean. I didn't find him
attractive at first,
我的意思是 开始我并不喜欢他
You know because he's not handsome
in the typical way.
他不是帅哥
But, um...
不过
...I don't know... now I
find him kind of... sexy.
现在我觉得他有点性感了
Hi.
你好
Did I get the day wrong?
我看错日期了吗
No. Why?
没有啊 怎么了
Because you're wearing pajamas?
你穿的睡衣啊
It's just brunch. It's Sunday.
I like to be comfortable.
星期天 刚吃完早午餐 这样比较舒服
- Oh, good. Okay. - Come on in.
-好吧 -进来吧
I got us that.
我带的酒
- I'll make us some mimosas. - Ok.
-我去弄点含羞草 -好的
This is nice. Thank you.
很好啊 谢谢
You carry a purse?
你的包吗
No, that's my daughter Tess's.
不 是我女儿泰斯的
It was outrageously expensive, but
it was her 18th birthday, so...
出奇的贵 不过是她十八岁生日送给她的
Oh, my God! Bagels!
天哪 百吉饼
I love bread. I really love it.
我大爱面包
So, what's she like? Your daughter.
你女儿怎么样
She's very sophisticated... as
you can tell by the pocketbook.
她很老成 就像教科书里面讲的一样
"Pocketbook".
教科书啊
She's smart, lovely and funny,
and she's moving to New York.
她聪明 可爱 风趣 她要搬去纽约了
Very far away.
非常非常远
It is far.
是很远
She's going to Parsons
School of Design.
她要去帕森斯大学念设计
I'm very proud of her.
她让我很骄傲
I bet. I would be.
肯定啊 要我也会
But part of me thinks
that I shouldn't let her go.
不过我又不舍得让她走
She's 18 and this is
a great opportunity for...
她十八岁 这是个很好的机会
...but if something
happens to her...
如果在纽约有什么事情发生的话
...while she's in New York,
I will never forgive myself.
我不会原谅自己的
Come on. But I know what you mean.
我理解你的心情
This whole going away to college thing.
上大学这事
We just send them off? And not
know where they are all the time?
我们就让他们离开 我们还不知道他们的情况
Aside from the fact that I don't know
而且我还不知道
what my life will be like when she's gone.
我女儿走了我的生活会变怎样
And Ellen doesn't want her dad and me
艾伦都不想让我们送她
to take her there. She wants us to take her...
她只想我们送她到
...to the airport here,
but don't fly with her.
机场 但是不能和她一起去
That would kill me...
just put her on the plane?
让她自己去还不如杀了我
Heartbreaking. That's the word for.
心碎就是就来形容这种心情的吧
We're going to have to develop hobbies. I think.
我们得培养点兴趣爱好
Yeah, I guess so.
我想是吧
Because I have already have one,
'cause I knit.
我已经织毛衣这个兴趣了
So I'll just spend the rest of my
life knitting. That's my plan.
所以我的计划就是织毛衣度过我余生
That's funny because...actually, I weave.
说起来奇怪 因为我也会织
Like baskets?
织篮筐吗
- Yeah, I do it in the garage. - Really!
-对啊 我在车库里织 -真的吗
No.
肯定不是啊
Why would you think I'd weave?
为什么会认为我会织东西啊
I thought you were...
I didn't want to insult you.
我以为你 我没有别的意思
- I'm kind of glad you don't weave. I have to say.
- Me, too.
-你不会真是太好了 -我也是
You know, I've been picturing what it's going
to be like for her not to be here.
我一直在想没有她在的日子会是怎样的
Even though she's only here half
the time, it'll be very different.
虽然她只呆三四天 也是个巨大的改变啊
Look. I can see your penis.
我看到你丁丁了
What? My God!
什么 我的天
Your pajama thing is a little bit open.
你的睡衣太透了
Shit! I'm very sorry.
擦 不好意思
What did you think?
你觉得怎么样
I think you are very healthy.
我觉得你很健康
Thank you.
谢谢
Go change your pants. Ok?
换条裤子行吗
Be right back.
马上就好
What happened to you guys? Not
the details, obviously, just general...
你们怎么了 大概说一下就好 不要细节
We were... very different.
我们非常不一样
We never had sex. Not my choice.
我们没有嘿咻过 不是我不想要
She just had no interest in it.
而是她没有性趣
And I'm pretty sure she had an affair.
我敢肯定她外面有人了
Which was awful,
太不爽了
because it meant
that she did like sex,
因为这说明她喜欢嘿咻的
she just didn't like it with me.
只是不喜欢和我做爱
You. Right.
你是对的
She thought my job was stupid.
她认为我的工作太愚蠢了
She thought I parented badly.
I thought she parented badly.
我们互相指责对方不会养小孩
Why are you wrecking my backyard?
你为什么在搞破坏
You have a lot of weeds.
太多杂草了
I thought this was all good.
这很好啊
No.
不
We never had sex, either. Not his choice.
我们也没有嘿咻过 也不是他的问题
We were pretty out of
sync in that department.
我们是不同世界的人
We were pretty out of sync
with Ellen, too. Oh, my God...
跟艾伦在一起的时候我们也没有相同的频率
...fought all the time
about how to parent.
关于如何养育小孩争的你死我活
That's good grass you're pulling up.
你拔的不是杂草
I'll put it back.
我放回去
Jesus.
老天
Got yourself a...
你脚上
...blister thing going on?
起泡了吗
Yeah.
是的
Are you grossed out?
你觉得恶心吗
No.
没有
You are. Are you
freaked out by my feet?
你有 你害怕看我的脚吗
I have a little problem with feet.
有一点
Have you looked at your own feet?
那你有看过你自己的脚吗
I'm used to my feet.
自己的无所谓
Okay, well...
好吧
What's the deal?
为什么
It has to do with my mother.
跟我妈有点关系
She had feet?
她脚臭吗
She had spectacular feet.
她有双令人过目不忘的脚
Here we go.
洗耳恭听啊
They were red and
yellow and green
青一块紫一块的
and purple and
swollen with veins.
还有肿大
I get it.
我懂了
Don't do that.
你不用穿上鞋啊
I have to. I've never had a pedicure.
我必须穿啊 我从来没有修过指甲
I never saw the point until this actual moment.
除非有毛病我从来不管它
Would you like a Band-Aid?
你要创可贴吗
Please! That would be great.
那太好了
And maybe a bag for my foot.
再来个袋子包住我的脚吧
Stop it.
别傻了
Two bags. Two bags for the old bag.
拿两个好替换啊
I knew I shouldn't have told you.
我就知道不该告诉你的
They're naked, right?
他们裸着的 对吧
Yeah.
是的
Are you ever attracted to them?
你有被他们吸引吗
No. I never.
不会
I'm sure they're attracted to you.
他们肯定对你有兴趣
Well I don't know. They're getting massaged.
这我就不清楚了 他们是来做按摩的
Do they ever hit on you?
他们有挑逗你吗
Sometimes, yeah.
有时候会
I can give you a massage
some time, if you want.
如果你需要的话改天给你按摩下
I think I might like that.
我很有兴趣
But I would definitely hit on you.
不过我觉得会挑逗你的
That might be okay.
没问题啊
Really?
真的吗
Want a kiss?
可以亲你吗
Yeah.
可以
You didn't actually open your
eyes at any point, did you?
你没有睁开你眼镜 对吧
No. No worries.
不需担心
I kept my eyes closed.
我没睁开眼
I figured...
我想着
...if I couldn't see you,
you couldn't see me.
你看不到我 我也看不到你
Oh, I saw you.
我偷看了你
Oh, God.
天哪
I'm tired of being funny.
我讨厌幽默的自己
Me, too.
我也是
But you're not funny.
可是你又不幽默
I'm so excited for you.
He sounds really great.
我为你感到高兴 他听起来很不错
He is great. It was so cute...
he made a whole bruncheon.
他是不错 他还做了早午餐
- Sweet. - Yeah, it was sweet.
-好贴心啊 -对啊
Okay, good.
好了
We had such good sex.
嘿咻的感觉太棒了
How fun. I can't even imagine.
难以想象
What do you think?
你觉得怎么样
I liked how it was before. You're going
to give yourself a hernia. You know.
我喜欢以前摆放的样子 不要放弃治疗
Okay, you guys are done.
Thanks for your help.
好了 不用你们帮忙了 谢谢你们
Take your drawing
in the kitchen.
拿上你们的画去厨房
You can watch TV,
but no Cleveland Show.
可以看电视 不过不能看克里夫兰秀
Please, Mom?
妈妈 求你了
Okay.
好吧
Jeez. Way to put your foot down.
天啊 你应该坚定立场的
I'm too tired to be a good parent.
当父母太累了
Maybe because you're always
moving furniture around.
也许是因为你总是爱摆弄家具
- Hi, Cathy! - Hola.
-凯茜你好 -好啊
You have no idea. Will
refused to fire her...
你绝对不知道 威尔不肯炒了她
...so I let it go, hoping she'd
get better. But she got worse.
我也不管了 希望她能更好点 但是她变本加厉
It was like she wanted to be fired.
She did such dumb stuff.
她想做些蠢事 让我们炒了她
That is so interesting, isn't it?
好有趣 不是吗
So I fired her. And she started crying.
Then I started crying.
所以我解雇了她 她开始哭 我也哭
Then we were hugging and...
I hired her back.
然后我们用拥抱着 我又把她请回来了
Of course you did. See, cause you're nice.
这就是你的作风 因为你是个老好人
Right? Some people would see
me as being compassionate
会吗 他们都认为我富有同情心
or soft-hearted or whatever.
或者心太软什么的
Will thinks I'm a baby.
威尔觉得我还是个孩子
He wants me to fire her again
as a learning experience!
他想我炒了她当成学习
Jesus Christ!
我的天哪
That's our relationship.
我们的关系就这样
- Come on, this is not your whole
relationship. - Whatever.
-拜托 你们又不是一直这样 -管它呢
He's a middle child who never got
enough fried chicken at dinner table
他就是个没人爱的孩子 永不满足
and needs everything to be fair.
还希望事事公平
Miss Sarah? Where should I put this?
It was in the bathroom.
莎拉女士 这个应该放哪 在厕所发现的
Outside, with the
ping pong table.
放外面的兵乓球桌上
Okay. No problem.
好的
Jesus.
天啊
Wow.
哇
I've never actually seen wisdom teeth.
我还没见过智齿呢
You do have a lot of fillings.
你有牙体缺失啊
Do you think they are the mercury kind, though?
你觉得严重吗
The normal kind.
一般
And a couple of crowns.
还有几个齿冠
Yeah. Okay, your turn.
好吧 该你了
Well, I'd rather you didn't.
我 还是算了吧
Well, I'd rather I did.
我就要
Excuse me, I'm going to get my glasses.
我先拿下眼睛
- Come on. - No. - Open your mouth! - No.
-张嘴 -不要 -张嘴啊 -不要
- Open your mouth. - Make me.
-张嘴 -你想办法啊
Make me.
想办法啊
- Open your mouth. - Okay.
-张嘴 -好
Oh, my God! You're missing a tooth?
天哪 你少了一颗牙齿
- You are! - Yes, I am.
-真的 -对啊
Let me see.
让我看看
You can't tell... it's way back there.
It doesn't matter.
没多大问题
I need some kind of hideous bone graft.
需要做个可怕的植骨手术
It costs a lot of money and I'm putting it off.
费用太高了 没做
My grandma Dee Dee had that.
我奶奶迪迪做过
Your grandma Dee Dee.
Thank you for that. Thanks.
你奶奶迪迪 谢谢
Oh, I'm so sorry!
抱歉
It's okay. This is Ellen's best friend,
Chloe. This is my friend, Albert.
没关系 她是艾伦的闺蜜克洛伊 这是我朋友艾伯特
Hi.
你好
Ellen didn't answer my texts.
So I thought maybe she was sleeping.
艾伦没有回我短信 我以为她还在睡觉呢
She's at her dad's, honey.
Is everything okay?
她在她爸爸那 有什么事吗
I thought we were go out
getting breakfast.
我们约好出去吃早饭的
You hungry?
你饿了没
Let's see. From 1975, Channel 4.
我想想 一九七五年的第四频道有什么节目
Well, what time?
什么时间
Oh, come on.
别闹了
Saturday morning.
星期六早上
Woody Woodpecker, Pink Panther,
McDuff, the Talking Dog...
《啄木鸟伍迪》 《粉红豹》 《麦克达夫》 《会说话的狗》
...which I didn't
like but watched anyway,
虽然我不喜欢 不过还是看了
Monster Squad,
Land of the Lost, then...
《怪物小分队》 《失落的大陆》 然后是
...Big John, Little John, which was
like the movie Big, but much weirder.
《大小约翰》很像电影《巨大》 不过更怪异些
Ok, That's incredible.
太不可思议了
I thought I watched a lot of TV!
我以为我看的电视够多了
I looked forward to that lineup.
我以前会看电视节目表
What, were you neglected as a kid?
什么 你是没人照看的小孩吗
I was kind of raised like a veal.
我就像放养的小牛一样
I was put in a dark room...
关进黑屋
...fed and told not to move.
有吃的 叫我别乱走
Very relaxing.
神清气爽啊
...and she's like, "I
might want to get another size",
她说 我想要其他的尺码
but that's bullshit, it is the right size.
那是扯淡啊 明明就是正确的尺码
She's petite, but very heavy
on top, so I got a medium!
她身材娇小 可是上围很大 所以给了她中码
But here's the thing,
I got it at Nordstrom Rack,
后来又悲剧了 我在诺德斯特龙折扣店买的
but I put it in a Neiman Marcus box...
却放进了尼曼的盒子里
Oh, yeah, that's good.
很好
Don't open the door.
最好别开门
Just pretend you don't know I'm here...
就假装你不知道我来了
...even though you heard me lock my car.
虽然你听到了我关车门的声音
Wow!
哇
Amazing.
太棒了
So what do you do with all this?
你们拿着干吗的
- Do you really want to hear this?
- Yeah. I do. What?
-你真的想听吗 -对啊 怎么了
I make sure things are
transferred to digital properly.
我确保它们转化成电子版
I make sure they're logged in properly.
I write blurbs...
确保它们正常播放 我还写它们的简介
...so if anyone under 50 wants to
put down their phone and come in...
当有五十岁以下的人想过来
...and watch something original and brilliant,
they can find it what they are looking for.
找原版的话 他们就可以找到他们想要的东西
Like what, for instance?
比如说
The Sid Caesar show.
The Jack Benny show.
《席德·西泽秀》《杰克·本尼秀》
The Dean Martin show.
《狄恩·马汀秀》
- So cool. - Yeah, it is.
-好棒啊 -对啊
I kind of love it.
我乐在其中
On slow days...
无聊的时候
...I can sit downstairs on my office and
watching couple episodes of What's Happening!!
我就会坐在办公室 看几集《发生什么了》
No, you don't.
你在开玩笑
Well, if things...
如果
This is my office.
这是我办公室
That's Bob. Hey.
那是鲍勃
- What about Flipper? Did you ever
see Flipper? - Of course I did.
-你看过《海豚的故事》（1996年上映美国家庭冒险片）吗 -当然
Oh, God. It made me want a
dolphin as a pet so bad.
当时好想要一只海豚当做宠物啊
Really? That's a lot of work.
真的吗 那要费很多功夫啊
What is that noise?
那是什么声音
Somebody watching something.
It happens occasionally.
有人在看伤感的电影 不足为奇
It's Taxi. The episode
where Alex's dog dies.
这是《的士速递》 这里阿历克斯的狗狗死了
Buddy or Buster or something.
狗狗是他的兄弟
- You hungry? - Yeah I'm starving.
-饿了吗 -饿死了
Let's get lunch.
吃中饭去吧
There she is! Right on time.
她来了 真准时
- Hi, honey. - Hi, Dad.
-好啊 -好啊 爸爸
So, Eva...
这是伊娃
Tess. Tess, Eva.
这是泰斯
Hi. Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你
So nice to meet you, too.
我也是
Seriously?
真的在这家吃吗
They have great chili!
它们家的辣椒很棒啊
I love Chili.
我喜欢辣椒
Have you ever been to Lilly's?
你们有去过丽丽那吃过吗
No.
没
It's so good.
It's right around the corner.
妙不可言啊 就在这附近
Lilly's it is.
那就去那吧
I'll be studying fashion design.
我学的是时装设计
You obviously have good taste.
你的品位不错
Thank you.
谢谢
Eva has a daughter your age going
to college in the fall also.
伊娃的女儿也是在秋天去上大学
She's going to Sarah Lawrence.
她去莎拉劳伦斯学院
She's interested in English and history.
She loves history!
她对英文和历史很感兴趣 特别是历史
I think she wants to be a writer.
她想成为一名作家
But Sarah Lawrence is
not what it used to be.
但是莎拉劳伦斯和以前大不相同了
I mean, I'm sure it's still good.
我的意思是还是挺不错的
It's just gone downhill a lot in the
last few years. Some of my, um...
只是最近几年在走下坡路 我的一些
...let's just say not-so-smart
friends just got in. I was shocked.
不怎么聪明的朋友都被录取了 我简直不敢相信
-Well. I'm sure a lot of smart people
still go there. - Oh, yeah.
-我相信还是会有才华的人的 -对啊
I know. I'm just saying.
我只是说说而已
I think you should stay
home and go to school here.
我还是愿意你上这边的大学
At least you're honest about it.
至少你说的是真心话
Mom acts like she's excited to be on
her own again, but I don't buy it.
妈妈就假装很兴奋可以享受一人生活了 我才不信
Why don't we take it a little easy on Mom.
Ok? She's all right.
对你妈好点 她很不错的
And maybe you should judge till you
have kids of your own.
也许你有小孩就懂了
Except I'm not having any.
可惜的是我不想要孩子
And why do you say that?
何出此言
I want a career.
我是事业型的
Anyway, I hate kids.
也不喜欢孩子
Really?
真的假的
Right now we have that in common.
跟我想法一样
Corey?
科里
Listen, she doesn't know
what she's talking about.
她在说胡话呢
She's too young to know what she wants.
We don't have to worry.
她还太小了 成熟了就明白了
Dad, I'm going to go
get a coffee, okay?
爸 我去喝咖啡了
Bye. Thank you for lunch.
拜拜 谢谢你的午饭
- So nice to met you. - You, too.
-见到你真好 -我也是
Yeah. Great.
很好
- Bye! - Bye.
-拜拜 -下次见
Be careful!
小心点
She has a lot of friends.
她朋友好多啊
You think she has threesomes?
你觉得她会3P吗
What? Why would you say that?
什么 为什么这么说
I know, but apparently, it's
what they're doing these days.
他们年轻人都爱这个啊
That's what I heard.
我听说的
Oh, my God.
天哪
Right?
很震惊 对吧
I'm afraid that window's closed.
恐怕那扇窗户关上了
There was a window?
有窗户吗
How was the daughter?
他女儿怎么样
Kind of awful, actually. A real snob.
说实话 感觉不好 好假啊
That's too bad.
太糟糕了吧
I wonder what your roommate will be like?
我在想你室友会是怎么样的
Me, too.
我也是
You want me to call her parents?
你想我和他们父母先联系吗
No, I don't.
不要
You hungry, honey?
你饿了吗
Not really.
还没
What did you eat yesterday?
你昨天吃的什么
I don't know.
不知道
Well, think. Tell me.
I want to know what you ate.
我想知道你昨天吃了什么
Cereal...
麦片
...a banana...
一根香蕉
- Where'd you get the banana?
- Mom, you're crazy!
-你在哪吃的香蕉 -妈妈 别乱想
What?
什么
What'd you have for lunch though?
那中午吃的什么
Okay, bye.
好了 我要走了
Where are you going?
你要去哪
I mean, he's kind of flabby and
middle-aged, but I don't care.
我的意思是 他中年了又很肥 不过我不介意
I'm flabby and middle-aged.
我也和他一样
It's funny, because our
middle-agedness is...
搞笑的是我的中年
...comforting, and sexy to me.
对我来说是件很舒适愉快的一件事
Isn't that so incredibly sad?
But sort of good too.
是不是很悲催 不过同时也很好
Yeah. I think that my ex, all he
wanted was for me to accept...
对啊 我前夫就是
...his belly and all of his quirks.
大肚子 还有一堆怪癖
In the end, I was completely
repulsed by him sexually.
后来是完全没性趣
Kind of terrible in bed
and just very clumsy.
性生活太不和谐了
Oh, god no.
不会吧
Just a sec.
等等
Here. It's my last copy, but I
really want you to have it.
这是我最后一本书 不过我想给你
Wow! Are you sure?
真的吗
- Absolutely. - Oh, wow.
-真的啊 -哇
I'm a little intimidated. I'm
not really good with poetry.
有点不安啊 我不太懂诗歌啊
Just let it wash over you.
Don't try to understand it.
让它灌溉你就好 不用理解
I won't, believe me.
God, thank you so much!
相信我 我不会的 非常感谢
- I've loved our time together.
- I know.
-我们相处的很融洽啊 -是啊
Do you think it would be weird
if we hung out as friends?
你觉得我们以朋友的身份出去玩会不会很奇特
I would love that! I would!
不会啊 很好啊
I want you to try this salsa,
'cause these tomatoes are amazing.
尝尝这沙拉吧 这西红柿太棒了
But careful! There's a ton of onions.
注意里面有很多洋葱
One of the many upsides to my divorce.
我离婚之后的一大好处
- What do you mean? - My ex hated
onions, so he would take a chip...
-什么意思 -我前夫讨厌洋葱 他会拿块薯片
...and he would put it in the
salsa and tap, tap, tap...
放到沙拉里
...swirl, tap, tap, tap,
swirl, and so on,
鼓捣鼓捣
until all the onions
were pushed...
直到洋葱
...up against the side!
都在一边
It kind of made me sick.
简直不能忍受
Mom?
妈妈
That's my daughter... she's not
feeling well. Be right back.
那是我女儿 她不太舒服 等等
- Hi, honey. - Hi.
-宝贝 -好啊
I don't feel good.
我不舒服
- I feel... Right here. - Let me see.
-就在这 -我看看
They're swollen.
有点肿大
Listen, will you come meet my friend?
Just for a second, please?
见见我朋友 就一会
Eva?
伊娃
你在哪
That's so weird, she was just here. Eva?
太奇怪了 刚刚还在这的 伊娃
I'm going back to bed.
我睡觉去了
- I love you. - I love you, too.
You have bad breath.
-爱你 -我也爱你 你口臭啊
I'm sick!
我生病啊
God!
天哪
Hi.
你在这啊
This planting I'm
admiring, it's so huge!
这课树好大啊
Thank you.
谢谢
I wanted you to meet my
daughter Tess, but...
我想让你见见我女儿泰斯的 不过
I have to go.
我有其他事情要做
Okay!
哦
Yeah. Okay.
好的
Great!
很好
All right.
好的
So I'll call you next week and
we'll do something. Ok?
下周电话联系 好吗
Wonderful. Thank you so much!
很好 谢谢
It was so nice!
太好了
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
Have a great day.
玩的愉快
Great, great, great!
很愉快
Bye-bye.
拜拜
- You okay? - I got it!
-还好吗 -没事
Do you believe that?
I am not shitting you!
你相信吗 我可没有吓你
That is an unbelievable coincidence.
What you gonna do?
太巧合了吧 当时怎么想的
I don't know!
大脑一片空白
Oh, shit! Your light went on.
Can you call me back, please?
该死 你又有病人了 待会再聊吧
Hi, Mom!
妈妈
Hi! Did you take your shoes off?
你脱鞋了吗
No. Since when do I have to?
没有 什么时候需要脱鞋了啊
We're doing that now. It's cleaner.
And your socks, too.
现在 这样更干净 还有袜子也脱了
You are not going to believe this.
你们绝不会相信的
It turns out that the woman I've
been massaging is Albert's ex-wife.
我按摩的那女的居然是艾伯特的前妻
- Weird! - So weird.
-狗血啊 -非常狗血
I have been listening to her say the
worst things about the one guy...
我听她说着
...I started to really, really like.
我刚有好感的人的坏话
And I pictured the ex she was
talking about as this fat...
我还在想着她前夫一副
...irritating slob...
肥头大耳的样子
...and it turns
out it's Albert!
没想到居然是艾伯特
Fat Albert!
肥猪艾伯特
What? Who?
什么 谁啊
It's a cartoon. A cartoon!
我说动画片呢
But he's so not like that.
但是他不想是这样啊
How do you know?
你怎么知道
We had breakfast the other day.
He's sweet, funny.
那天我们一起吃的早饭 他很幽默风趣啊
Yeah, you liked him, right? Did you like him?
你也喜欢他 对吧
- Totally. - Wait, what?
-绝对啊 -等等 什么
You weren't here, honey.
We all had breakfast. That's all.
那天你不在 我们一起吃的早饭
I haven't even met him.
我还没过他呢
Well, you will.
有机会的啦
- What did she say about him?
- Oh, my God!
-她说他什么坏话了 -天哪
It's like this parade of horribles!
He's disgusting.
简直贬到一无是处啊 很恶心啊
That he's like this clown in bed.
床上技术很烂
Mom! Oh, my God!
妈妈 别说这么露骨
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
不好意思
I date sometimes. It's just
so hard to meet people.
我约过几次会 不过机会不多
And I'm not attracted to anybody.
而且很难喜欢上别人
- Really? - Really.
-真的吗 -真的
And you weren't attracted
to your ex-husband?
你也没有喜欢过你前夫吗
That must have been difficult.
这太糟糕了吧
Well, I tried
really hard. I did.
我试着去接受过的
But he would go on so many diets,
and then he would cheat...
他骗我说他都在吃素食
...and then he would act
shocked when he got fatter.
实际上没有 对于变胖这个事实
...the behavior
around the weight.
他也是无所谓
Excuse me.
打扰下
Are you Marianne Hope?
你是玛丽安妮·霍普吗
Yes.
对
- Oh, my God! - I told you.
-我的天哪 -跟你说了是她吧
We were just talking about you.
You are like our biggest idol.
我们刚还说到你呢 你是我们的偶像
This means so much to us.
你的书对我们的生活太重要了
She gave me a copy of Beautiful
Fruit when my mom died.
我妈妈去世的时候她给了我一本《美丽果实》
It saved me.
它让我挺过来了
How wonderful. I'm so sorry.
太好了 很遗憾听到你妈妈去世的消息
Oh, thank you.
谢谢
Well, thanks very much. Blessings.
非常感谢 祝你好运
Blessings.
好运
Take care. Blessings!
祝你们好运
It's so cool that you saved her.
你是活菩萨啊
But, he never got obese, right?
不过他没有肥胖症 对吗
Well, it depends on your
definition of the word obese.
那要看你的理解啦
But initially, um... you were...
刚开始 你是有
...I don't know, you
liked him, more or less?
你或多或少有喜欢他的吧
Unfortunately... less.
很少
There were just so many things
that really got on my nerves.
很多事情我都看不惯
Like what, though?
比如说
Sorry I'm being so negative.
I really am.
抱歉 我又消极了
But it's okay. It is.
没事啊
It's just that I don't really have anybody
我没有朋友
I can bitch to about things like this.
可以让我抱怨这些事
You can completely bitch to me. Really.
你可以向我吐苦水啊
- Thank you. - Oh, sure.
-谢谢 -没关系啊
I trust you.
我很信任你
Oh, god.
天哪
I do.
真的
What's wrong with you?
She can find another masseuse.
你什么毛病啊 她可以另找一个按摩师啊
I'm her friend. She doesn't
have any close friends.
我是她朋友 她没有好朋友
I'm like it.
我喜欢和她在一起的感觉
I feel so pulled in.
She's like a human Trip Advisor.
我深陷其中不能自拔 -她就像人生导师一样
Albert is not a hotel.
艾伯特又不是旅馆 你看看别人的评价就做出选择
But if you could avoid staying
in a bad one, wouldn't you?
可是有机会了解下也不是坏事啊
Oh, my God.
天哪
She has said so many
bad things about him.
她说了他很多坏习惯
She's not perfect.
她也并非善类
But she knows what she's talking about.
She's smart.
她知道她在说什么 她不傻
So are you.
你也是啊
Maybe she's ultimately right.
也许她是对的
Are you right about Peter? Couse you just didn't
want him... does that make him unlovable?
那彼得呢 就因为你不爱他了 他就一无是处了吗
By anyone normal.
还是有人会喜欢他的
You haven't said anything about
my furniture arrangement.
我家具摆放的怎么样
I don't remember how it was before.
我都忘了原来怎么样
Hey! What do you think?
你觉得怎么样
Oh, honey. Why do you keep doing this?
亲爱的 你有强迫症啊
She's filling a hole.
她在排遣空虚呢
I'll fill your hole.
放着我来
Different hole.
别乱想
You're missing out. Fun time!
机不可失失不再来 好好玩吧
Hi!
你好
Whose car is this?
谁的车啊
Tess is getting hers fixed.
This is a rental.
泰斯的车拿去修了 这是租的
Sorry.
不好意思
Why do you have it?
那怎么在你这
I'm letting her drive mine.
She likes it better.
我让她开我的 她更喜欢我的车
Yeah, I bet she does.
肯定啊
- You okay? - Yeah.
-可以吗 -没问题
What was that?
那是什么
The gear skrinkle.
车子在卖萌呢
"Skrinkle?"
卖萌啊 （skrinkle查不到 因为汽车有发出声音 所以这样翻译）
Why are you shaking that?
干吗要晃它
It spreads the butter around.
把黄油弄均匀
You put more butter on that?
你要了很多黄油吗
No, I put regular butter. I asked
for butter. I didn't put more butter.
没有啊 就一般的量啊
Oh, I thought it came with butter.
哦 我以为原来就有的呢
This actor, this guy, I saw him in a restaurant.
这个演员 我在餐厅见过他
He was about three and a half feet tall.
三尺半的身高
You need to whisper, okay?
轻点声 好吗
What is she wearing?
It looks like her aunt
她穿的什么啊 好像她姨妈
crocheted something
to put over like a plant or something.
在编什么搭在盆栽上
Shh!
嘘
You got to whisper.
小点声
I am whispering.
我是轻声说的啊
- I'm whispering. - No.
- 我是轻声说的啊 - 你没有
I want to ask you something.
我问你些事情
And I really want the truth.
我要你实话实说
Okay.
问吧
Can you breathe when I'm on top of you?
我压着你还能呼吸吗
Yeah!
可以啊
I'm planning on losing some weight.
By the way. I know I need to.
是时候开始减肥了
- Was it an issue with your ex-wife?
- Oh, my God!
-你前妻也抱怨过这个问题吗 -天啊
Sometimes I ate just to drive her nuts.
有时候我吃的东西也会让她不解
You have a cold?
你感冒了吗
No. No, I...
不 没有
I broke my nose a couple times.
我鼻子受过几次伤
My doctor says at this point,
my nose is purely ornamental.
医生说我鼻子已经没有实际用处了
Will you get it fixed?
想要做手术吗
Yeah, after the missing tooth.
要啊 先把牙齿弄好再说
You know, I think Tess really liked you.
我觉得很泰斯喜欢你
I could tell.
能感觉出来
She seems so neat.
她很好
She really is a great girl.
她很不错的
I know she can be obnoxious
sometimes, but...
只是有时候很讨人嫌 不过
...she's young. She's really got
a good heart. She's gonna figure it out.
她的出发点是好的 她还小 她长大后会明白的
I kind of adore you already.
我被你迷住了
So what about you and Chris?
What's going on there?
你和克里斯怎么样啦
What? What?
说啊
We did it.
我们嘿咻了
Really?
真的吗
How was it?
感觉怎么样
Nice. I think.
很好啊 其实
No, it was good.
是很棒
Congratulations. I'm happy it was nice.
恭喜啊 我很高兴
Even if we don't stay together,
I'm glad I got it over with.
就算我们分开了 我也不会后悔
I'm glad I took your advice.
感谢你的建议
Hey! Hi, honey.
你回来啦
When did you get here?
你什么时候到的
A couple of minutes ago.
Just waiting for you.
刚到 在等你呢
Look.
呃
I've wanted to paint your
nails for like ten years.
我早就想帮你涂指甲油了
I thought you were too ticklish.
我以为你只是怕痒呢
I know!
我是啊
She's in love.
她恋爱了
So I guess that makes you not
ticklish anymore.
爱情的力量的无穷的啊
You weren't here. Come be with us.
你刚才没在 来聊聊吧
Actually, I have some...
其实我有一些
Come on, Ellen. Come back.
别走啊 艾伦
Crazy day.
疯狂的一天
I had a wonderful call from
Joni Mitchell this morning.
今早接到琼尼·米切尔的电话
She read the galleys to my new collection
and loved them, so that was...
她去看了我的展览并给了好评
You're friends with Joni Mitchell?
你是琼尼·米切尔的朋友吗
Yeah, we have been for a while.
Do you want some water?
对啊 认识她有一阵子了 要喝水吗
No, thank you.
不用 谢谢
And I met a guy! A really nice guy.
我遇见一个非常不错的男人
He takes really good care
of himself. He's vegan...
他非常懂得照顾自己 他是素食主义者
...and he actually read
my work before he met me.
他有看过我的书
A poetry-reading vegan. Oh, my God!
我的天哪 会读诗歌的素食者
I hope it goes well.
希望能有个好结果
I tend to get my hopes up a little early.
我的希望又重燃了
I just don't want to be disappointed again.
不要再让我失望就好
With Albert, there was always
this bait and switch going on、
艾伯特让我失望透了
When we first started dating, I thought,
第一次约会的时候 我还想
"Oh, he's mature. He can buy a house."
他是土豪啊 还有钱买房子
- This house? - Yes!
- 这栋房子吗 - 是的
But you should see where he lives now.
And he made...
看看他现在的家 还有他用
...this dish of spaghetti
with eggplant and mozzarella.
茄子和玛苏里拉奶酪做的意大利面
Sounds kind of delicious.
听起来很好吃的样子
But it turned out that
was all he could cook.
不过他只会做那一道
And he has no friends.
I mean, neither do I, but...
他没有朋友 我也没有 不过
Well, me and Joni.
我和琼尼是你的朋友啊
Yeah. That's true! That's true, that's true.
那倒是
Hi.
你好
- Hungry? - Yes.
-饿了吗 -是啊
Get ready for some
eggplant with mozzarella!
尝尝这意大利面
- You okay? - Yeah.
-你没事吧 -没事啊
Wow! This is actually delicious!
还蛮好吃的啊
Why do you sound surprised?
干吗这么惊讶
It's great.
很不错啊
How was work today?
今天工作怎么样
It was good.
很好
I had two massages.
有两位客人
Barnacles?
一言不发还是
Non-stop talking? Boners?
说个没完 还是勃起男
There was this nice woman in Santa Monica.
有一位来自圣莫尼卡的女士
She talked a lot about her ex-husband.
她说了很多关于她前夫的事
I just hope it wasn't my ex-wife.
不会是我前妻吧
I
我
I got you a little present.
我给你准备了个小礼物
You did?
是吗
Now, it's just a little present.
小礼物
Oh, my God!
天哪
I saw it and thought of you.
我一看到她就想到了你
This beautiful, wonderful...
这条美丽的
I can't do it, but let me help you.
我帮你带上吧
Oh, my God.
天哪
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
Look.
我戴着
Do you like it on me?
好看吗
It's nice.
很好看啊
Maybe I shouldn't have? Is it too soon?
现在送你这个是不是太早了
No. It's just so nice.
不会啊 我很喜欢
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh!
啊
- What? - Nothing.
-怎么了 -没事
- You all right? - Yeah. I don't
know what that was. Sorry.
-还好吧 -抱歉 不知道那是什么
- Let me get here. - You okay?
-我来吧 -确定没事吗
- Stop! Stop! -What?
- Your beard is so tickly.
-不要 -又怎么了 -你的胡子太刺人了
Sorry.
不好意思
That's okay.
没事
Okay, here I come again.
那继续吧
Oh, my hair! My hair, my hair!
我的头发
I don't know what I'm doing, but this
isn't going very well, so let's just stop.
不知道怎么了 要不下次吧
What?
怎么了
You look cute in my robe.
穿上我的睡袍很好看
- Is everything okay? - You have
like four hundred mouthwashes.
-没事吧 -你的漱口水也泰国了吧
Yeah, I need to use them and...
我需要就买了
...then I buy them and then I forget
about them and then I buy more of them.
不过我忘记我买过了 就又买了更多
And you have like 80 million toothbrushes.
牙刷也很多
I do?
有吗
I only use one of them.
我只用一只
So why don't you throw the other ones out?
那为什么不扔了其他的
I don't know. Because... they're my friends?
不知道 因为有感情了
Are you all right?
你还好吗
You want to take another shot at it?
要不要再试一次
I'm just... I'm kind of tired.
我有点累了
- Is that okay? - Totally.
-下次好吗 -可以啊
You looked so pretty.
你好美啊
Seriously, kiddo, I'm proud of you.
说真的 我非常骄傲
Thank you, Dad.
谢谢 爸爸
We are so proud.
我们都非常骄傲
We have some graduation money for you.
这是庆祝你毕业的奖金
Thank you, Fran, Dad.
谢谢你们
It's in fives.
全是五块的哦
Thank you for including me.
谢谢你们邀请我
You really have a fight with your mom?
你真和你吗吵架了啊
- Huge. - Where's your dad?
-大吵了一架 -你爸呢
He lives in San Diego, but
you'd think he was in Alaska.
他在圣地亚哥 不过好像他在阿拉斯加一样
He never visits.
他从不来看我
But I don't care.
不过我无所谓了
He remarried this really weird
woman, and she never talks.
他和一个好像哑巴的女人结婚了
Hear, hear for second marriages!
好好听听人家的经历
It's kind Of true, though.
不过有一点倒是真的
It's good when everyone is older and wiser.
年长的和更加睿智的会愈加适合
Steady.
更加稳定
Maybe second marriages work because
people have figured out how to compromise.
也许二次婚姻顺利的关键在于你不怎么计较了
Or behave. Perhaps.
或者懂得怎么样才是得体的
- Thank you very much.
- Nobody's talking about you.
-谢谢 -没人说你
Don't take it personally.
I'm talking generally.
别对号入座 我说的是一般情况
If I got married again, I'd be on the
lookout for the inevitable problems.
如果我要再婚的话 绝对不自找麻烦
Odd conversation. Pretty weird.
多么奇怪的谈话啊
Sorry, but maybe don't get
married a second time.
不好意思 我想你没有机会的
I'm not saying I will. I'm just saying.
我只是说说而已 何况鬼知道呢
She's just saying.
她只是随口说说
Fran, what was your ex-husband,
you first husband like?
弗兰 你前夫怎么样
Oh, he was actually a lovely, lovely man.
But not for me.
他其实是个很好的男人 只是不适合我
Very grownup!
很理性啊
He passed away. Two years ago.
他两年前去世了
Oh, I'm sorry.
不好意思
Sorry. Could we get some more bread, please?
可以帮我们再拿一些面包过来吗
- Please, no more bread. - Why not?
-不要面包啦 -为什么
- I don't want to eat it. - Then don't eat it.
-我吃饱了 -那就别吃啊
More bread, please.
再拿些面包
Are you even gonna eat it?
你还要吃吗
I don't know, but somebody else might want some.
不知道 不过其他人可能想吃啊
- I probably will. - Me, too.
-我想吃 -我也是
Bread eater, bread eater.
有两位想吃面包的啊
I'm sorry. So, Fran, you eat bread, I see.
所以 弗兰 你喜欢吃面包啊
It's true!
对啊
So that means you get to keep cookies
in  the house all the time.
所以说你们家一直都用饼干咯
I can.
可以啊
What are you guys talking about?
你们在说什么啊
It's not a big deal, but I have a little
trouble controlling myself...
没什么 不过我自控力不好
...so when Peter would
bring home things like...
每次彼得带回家的巧克力啊
...chocolate or good
bread, yummy stuff,
面包啊 或者其他好吃的
I'd eat all of it,
then I hate myself.
我都会吃的一干二净 之后我就后悔
And me for bringing it home
in the first place.
还有责怪我干嘛把他们带回家
So did you stop buying it?
所以你就再也不买了
- Yeah, I did. - And you got so angry.
-是的 -因为你生气了
- I was not angry. - A little bit angry.
-哪有 -绝对有
Well, he should have been angry.
他生气理所当然啊
Why should he be deprived because
she can't control herself?
为什么她自控力差就要他也陪着受罪
Because she's his wife and
he's trying to help her?
因为她是他老婆 想帮助她
Yeah, but is that really helping her?
但是这真的对她好吗
Yes!
当然
Not if we want her to
learn to control herself.
为什么不让她自己学习自控呢
"We?"
我们是指谁
I just said it's not fair to him.
我只是认为这对他不公平
Why does everything have to be fair?
What are you, six?
为什么每件事都要公平 你还当你是六岁小孩吗
Of course... What? Let's keep it nice.
当然 和善点好吗
I just forget the cookies are there. So...
我忘了那天还有饼干呢
That's why it's good you're
married to Peter and I'm not.
这就是为什么你适合彼得而我不适合了
That is absolutely the God's honest truth.
这是天意啊
Ooh, it's cold out.
外面好冷
Nobody ate the bread, by the way.
没人喜欢吃面包的
You did.
你就吃啦
Yeah, exactly.
那是
Exactly?
是吗
Let me ask you a question.
问你个问题
When people asked why we got
divorced, what do you tell them?
别人问起我们为什么离婚 你怎么说的
I say I don't think you and I
should have been together.
我说我们不适合
What about Fran? I mean you tell her
everything, you talk to her about us.
弗兰呢 你跟她说我们的事了吗
Right. She's your wife. Right.
看我多傻 她是你妻子 当然告诉了
Yeah, okay.
好吧
That was fun, huh?
刚才很高兴 对吧
I started this blanket
when you were five years old.
你五岁的时候开始织的这条毛毯
I don't know what I was
thinking about this color.
我也不懂怎么选这个颜色了
I'm going to finish it,
so you can take it with you.
我要把它打完 你就可以带着去上学了
I'll probably buy another one, in case.
以防万一 我还是买一条吧
What are you talking about?
This will be good.
你在说什么 这条可以用的
Why are you looking at this?
你看这个干吗
I don't know.
不知道
I just pulled it out.
我拿出来
I was trying to remember what I knew.
试着回忆我还记得的
Did I already know those
things about your dad?
那时候我真的了解你爸了吗
I mean the things we would fight about.
那些我们经常争吵的东西
Probably not.
可能没有
I think I did, actually.
我想我有
I think I always knew.
我一直都知道
Or felt them.
或者说感觉到了
I just wasn't paying attention.
我只是没注意
But look at what I got, huh?
但是我有你
- I'm going to bed. - No, stay
here and cozy up with me.
-我去睡觉了 -呆在这陪我啦
I'm tired.
我累了
Come on, Chloe.
克洛伊 快点
Is that hard?
这难吗
Not at all. You want to learn?
不会啊 想学吗
Yeah.
想
I've been trying to teach
Ellen for the longest time!
我一直想教艾伦
Albert.
是艾伯特
Are you still seeing his wife?
你还和他老婆有来往吗
Well, she has a bad shoulder.
And she has no friends.
她肩膀痛 她也没有朋友
What? Don't look at me like that.
别用这种眼神看我
I'm screwed up.
我搞砸了
Hold on just one second.
等一会
I'm in the middle of some bullshit.
我在处理一些破事
- Can you just put your table down? - Sure.
-Then we will...
-把你按摩椅放下吧 -好的 -然后我们再
I'll be right back.
我马上好
Yeah. Take your time.
慢慢来 别着急
We did, we agreed on it, Albert!
艾伯特 我们说好了的
Because I was there! I remember.
我在那 我记得非常清楚
Oh, my God. Okay. Well, it is.
It's all worked out.
天哪 好吧 就这样
Yes, it is. Okay, fine, good. Bye!
好 好 好 再见
My God, I cannot wait till I don't
have to talk to him anymore.
老天 什么时候才不用和他说话了
What happened?
发生什么了
He thinks he should take
Tess to school, not me.
他想带泰斯去学校
Tess wants it to be me, because she told me.
泰斯想让我去 她就是这样说的
But, I mean... Thank you. Can't
you both just take her?
可是 谢谢 为什么不一起去
I don't think so. No, I don't.
算了吧 我不想
He's such a wreck about her going away.
他非常不想她离开
She doesn't need that kind of energy right now.
这样对她不好
And he just focuses so much onto her.
She can feel it.
她可以感受他在紧看着她
Isn't that kind of nice, though?
这不是件好事吗
I mean, that he focuses?
我是说关心她
Well, maybe if he had a girlfriend or
something so it would balance it out...
或许他有个女朋友就会好点
...but I don't see that happening.
不过应该不可能
Really? Why not?
为什么
Because he's a loser.
因为他是屌丝
Uh-oh.
哦哦
Such a mean word, but it fits.
是很刻薄 不过形容他再适合不过了
How does it fit?
为什么
For instance... this is typically Albert...
比如说 这就是他的写照
...when we were first going out,
我们第一次出去的时候
he had nothing next to his bed.
他床边什么都没有
No table, nothing.
连张桌子都没有
At first I thought, "That's cute.
开始觉得很酷
It's kind of bohemian." Stuff like that.
有点放荡不羁的感觉
So then we got married and I went out
我们结婚之后 我去买了
and bought these really
lovely bedside tables.
个非常可爱的床头柜
Then last year, I saw all of his stuff
可是后来 他的东西
was on the side of the bed again.
又全部堆在床上
I mean, I took the tables, granted,
我拿走了柜子
but he never went out and replaced them.
他就放肆了
He's just content to just put
his shit on the floor again.
把东西直接扔在地上
Metaphorically speaking, he's not
building a life for himself.
他就是不懂得生活
I mean, who would date a person like that?
谁愿意和他在一起啊
Right.
对
I'm not picking up.
我不会接的
Marianne, please pick up the phone.
玛丽安妮 接电话好吗
We haven't resolved anything.
I know you're there.
这事还没解决呢 我知道你听到了
This is so embarrassing. I'm sorry.
不好意思 太囧了
Fine. Don't deal with it.
好吧 爱解决不解决
Okay, these are just little things.
这还是鸡毛蒜皮的小事
Ultimately, we just...
最后 我们
I never felt understood by him.
他根本就不了解我
You know?
你知道吗
He didn't get the poetry.
他不懂诗歌
He never got me.
也不懂我
Has anyone ever gotten you?
有人真正理解你吗
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道
What about the flabby guy?
那个肥男呢
How's that?
他理解你吗
Yeah. Maybe.
可能吧
I need you to meet him. We can do a
double date. Or something like that。
我需要你 我们来个四人约会吧
Not so you can decide what you think of him.
见一次面也不能看清他的真实面目啊
Please? I'm losing all perspective here.
拜托啦 我都不知道该怎么了
Exactly! You don't need somebody else's!
你自己搞定
Will you please just say yes
and do this for me? Please?
你就不能答应我一次吗 求你了
They had stars and suns and moons.
还有星星啊 太阳啊 月亮啊
I know. I hate those.
我懂 我也讨厌那些
Tell me why do women like things that look
like they belong to children?
为什么女人们都童心未泯呢
You know what I love? Dollhouse furniture.
I would eat it if I could.
知道我喜欢什么吗 玩具屋家具 要是可以吃的话我就吃了
Sometimes I wish I was single, just
so I could have girlie sheets.
有时候希望我还是单身 就可以用女生床单了
You would love that.
你一直都在想吧
I have flowery sheets. They're not
all they're cracked up to be.
我有花朵图案的床单
I like your flowery sheets.
我喜欢你的床单
Oh! Don't sell me out, man.
别这样说啊
We're new. I'd like her sheets if
they had little Mussolinis on them.
如果有墨索里尼在上面就更好了
Talk to me when you get night tables.
你打算什么时候买床头柜
He has normal sheets, but no night tables.
他的床单很正常 不过没有床头柜
So I don't have night tables.
我没有床头柜
Maybe it's a metaphor.
他开玩笑呢
Or maybe not!
或者是真的
I don't know.
我不知道
I make a million compromises. It just seems...
我做了很多妥协
...not having flowery
sheets is not a big deal.
不用花朵图案的床单也不是大事吧
I know. I know you make compromises.
我知道你做了很多牺牲
Really? What do you think they are?
真的吗 看看他们
This is not the time.
别在这说
I'm just saying sometimes I wish
I was with somebody
有时候我就在想要是和一个
who was more interested in history.
对历史感兴趣的人在一起该有多好
- What? - History.
-什么 -历史
Okay. I'm just saying.
好吧 我说说而已
- More guacamole? - Not for me.
-还要鳄梨沙拉吗 -我不要了
I'd love some, actually.
再给我来点
You know how many calories
are in guacamole?
你知道鳄梨沙拉多少卡路里吗
Ten.
十吗
Lay off the guy. He likes guacamole.
别管他啊 他喜欢就让他吃嘛
You know what? We don't need the guac!
不要鳄梨沙拉了
I'll just stick with the cheese.
我吃芝士就好
You know what I'm going to get you
as a present? A calorie book.
你知道我要送什么书给你吗 介绍卡路里的书
Please don't.
不要
Yeah. A calorie book as
a gift is not so good.
这好像不太好吧
Eva tells me you're a therapist.
伊娃说你是治疗师啊
Tell us about your weirdest patient.
跟我们说说最奇葩的病人
- No, I can't. - She can't.
-这有损医德 -她不能说的
Of course you can! You don't
have to name names, mate.
不要说名字不就行了吗
You're so uptight about confidentiality.
你还真是恪守原则啊
Shouldn't she be?
难道不应该吗
Well, you know. I mean.
我的意思是
Okay. I have one patient who
picks his nose and eats it.
好吧 有个病人挖鼻屎再吃下去
Oh, man!
天哪
- In front of you? - Yes.
-在你面前 -是的
Is he a child?
他是小孩吗
Are you making this up?
不会是你编的吧
It is so gross and distracting.
真的是太恶心了
He does it in this way he thinks I
can't see, but it's so obvious.
他以为我不知道 不过怎么可能
I won't say who it is, but he is famous.
我不说是谁 不过是个名人
- Really famous. - He is not!
-很有名 -不会吧
- I know who it is. - You do?
-我知道是谁 -你确定
- No, you don't. - I absolutely do.
-你不知道 -我肯定知道
Please, Sarah, tell us! Please!
莎拉 求求你告诉我们
Okay! That's it! Show's over!
好了 八卦到此为止
I like being drunk. I really think
it's do think it's highly overrated.
我喜欢喝醉的感觉 我绝对被高估了
Underrated!
不对 低估了我的酒量
You're shouting.
你太大声了
I am? No, I'm not.
有吗 没有啊
You are. A little.
有一点点大声
Okay, I'm sorry.
不好意思
I don't want to wake up the small people.
我不想吵到别人
I'm sorry.
对不起
You want to know something funny?
你知道什么才好笑吗
This one here can't whisper.
他不会轻声说话
What?
什么
Will you do it right now?
Will you show them?
你现在做给他们看啊
I'm whispering.
我在轻声说话
That was a whisper.
他会啊
Huh? What? No, it's not.
什么 那才不是
Can I?
我这是吗
Yeah, that was a whisper.
你可以
What about me?
我呢
Yes, you can whisper.
你也可以
This is whispering.
这次呢
No, it's not. That is not a whisper at all.
不 你根本就不能
- You're picking on him. - No, I'm not!
-你在找他茬 -我没有
You are.
你就是
You kind of are.
有一点
Okay, I'm sorry. I've just,
never in my entire life...
好吧 抱歉 只是我从来没有遇到过
...have I met anybody who
couldn't whisper at all.
一个人不会轻声说话的
Whatever.
好吧
No. You are not allowed to
complain about her anymore.
不 你不要再发牢骚了
Cathy? Did you put this in the drawer?
凯茜 你在柜子里放什么了
- Did you put this in the drawer? - No.
-是你放的吗 -不是
Maybe one of the kids did.
应该是小孩子放的
That actually could be this time.
非常有可能哦
But I think you put it there, 'cause I find
但是我认为是你放的 因为我一直都能在
weird stuff in these drawers all the time.
柜子里找到这些奇怪的东西
I clean the best I can.
我尽力了
I'm just trying to understand
the thought process.
我只想知道她是怎么想的
You like the counters clean.
你说桌面上不要放东西
Yeah, but not by shoving weird
shit in the wrong drawers.
可是不是叫你乱放啊
Does the ball belong in the kitchen?
How does that help me?
这垒球应该放在厨房吗 你这是帮倒忙
That's enough. I think we...
够了 我们
You know what, Mrs. Sarah?
莎拉女士
I find your crap everywhere.
你的东西乱扔
You think I know where to put it?
我哪里知道该放哪去啊
You leave stuff all over the house.
房间里全是你的东西
You let your children write on the walls.
小孩子在墙上画画
You floss your teeth and leave it.
你用完的牙线就直接扔那
You clean your own house.
老子不干了
You people disgust me. But you was nice, Mr. Will.
你让我恶心 威尔先生 你不错
Thanks, Cathy!
谢谢 凯茜
Really would have been kinder to fire her.
根本不用闹这么僵的
Oh, my God.
天哪
Guys, my timing
maybe be a little off...
也许这时候说这个不对
...but I think I put
the ball on the drawer.
我觉得我会把球放柜子里
Not funny.
这不好笑
Are you serious?
别开玩笑了
That wasn't a very fun evening, was it?
糟糕的一晚上 对吗
God! Yikes!
天哪
Why do you care if I don't
know how to whisper?
为什么你抓住我的缺点不放
What was that?
这是干吗啊
I mean, that was embarrassing.
这很尴尬啊
I was just joking around.
That was complete... nothing.
我只是拿你开涮而已 没有恶意
A calorie book?
一本卡路里的书
You're going to buy me a calorie book?
你准备送我一本卡路里的书
Okay, well, I'm sorry.
抱歉
I'm obviously not gonna
buy you a calorie book.
肯定不会送你啦
I thought you actually liked me.
我还以为你真的喜欢我呢
I do like you.
我是喜欢你啊
Why do I feel like I just spent
the evening with my ex-wife?
为什么我感觉你今晚我前妻附身一样
Wait, what are you doing,
driving me home?
你干吗 送我回家
Mmm-hmm.
对啊
Oh.
哦
Are you going to spend the night?
在我家住吗
No. Not tonight.
不 以后吧
Okay.
好
Hi.
好啊
Ellen went out with friends, but I didn't
really want to go home. Is this okay?
艾伦和朋友出去了 我不想回家 可以在你家睡觉吗
I'm glad you're here, actually.
有你在真好
I'm always so much more
comfortable at your house.
在你家我总是很安心
You know...
你可以
...you would be so welcome to stay
in Ellen's room once she's gone.
艾伦走了你可以住她房间啊
You'd have to check with your
mom, but the room will be empty.
你想回家就可以回去 反正房间没人住
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
-真的吗 -对啊
That would be awesome.
Thank you so much.
太棒了 谢谢
Sure.
没关系
Thank you.
谢谢
Excuse me, Chloe,
but can I have my mom back?
克洛伊 可以把我妈还给我了吗
Honey, we were just watching
something and we were just passed out.
宝贝 我们刚在看电影 就睡着了
Next you'll be asking her to
move into my room when I'm gone.
下一步你是不是准备我走了让她住进来
I'm sorry.
对不起
No, it's not your fault, sweetie.
不 不关你事
I better go home.
我还是回家吧
Honey.
宝贝
Chloe is needy.
克洛伊需要人爱
Who's needy?
那我呢
You know, I guess I am...
你知道我想
...just trying to feel
a little bit more separate.
有点独立的生活
Sort of prepare.
也在适应中
But instead, I just feel
lonely and anxious and...
不过 我却只感到孤单 焦虑
...Chloe is always here.
克洛伊又一直出现在家
I'm so sorry about that.
对不起
But, Ellen, you know you're my baby.
艾伦 你才是我的孩子啊
Right, honey? Give Mommy a hug.
Will you come sit with me?
对吧 抱我一个 过来坐坐好吗
Can I see what Daddy and Fran got for you?
给我看看弗兰和爸爸给了你什么
I'm going to finish my blanket.
我还是去织毛毯吧
They get you anything else?
还给了你什么
Oh, those are good. They don't
take up room. You'll use those.
很好 也不占空间 非常有用
Hey, did you ever get a
chance to look at my book?
你看了我的书吗
- Oh, I did! - You did?
-我看了 -真的吗
Yes. Your poems are beautiful!
你的诗太美了
I mean, not that I understand
them, but I like them.
我看不懂 不过我很喜欢
Thank you. And I'm sure you understand them.
谢谢 你可以看懂的
Mom!
妈妈
We're out here!
我们在外面
Dad's in the car. I forgot my phone.
爸爸在车上 我忘拿手机了
Good, because I finally get
to introduce you guys.
你们还没见面呢
This is Eva.
这是伊娃
Tess!
泰斯
Hi?
你好
You guys know each other?
你们认识吗
Uh, yeah, we know each other.
对啊
This is Tess.
这是泰斯
Mom, she's dating Dad.
妈 她和爸爸在一起
- What? - You didn't know that?
-什么 -你不知道吗
You date Albert?
你和艾伯特在一起
I'm not sure what's going on right now.
Wait a minute.
我糊涂了 等会
Hello! Marianne!
玛丽安妮
Sorry to interrupt, but, Tess,
we really have to get going.
打扰了 泰斯 我们得出发了
Hi!
你好
Hi.
好啊
I don't understand. What are you doing here?
你在这干吗
She massages me. We're friends.
她给我按摩啊 我们是朋友
I thought.
我以为
You're friends with Marianne.
你是玛丽安妮的朋友
I met you...
我在派对上见到你
...at a party and you gave me your card...
你给我了名片
No, no. I gave you my card.
错了 是我给了你名片
Yes. I think you were at that same party.
对 我们都参加了那个派对
Yeah, I remember the party.
我记起来了
And you met us both.
我们两个你都见过
So what now you're her masseuse?
所以你现在给她按摩 是吗
Yeah!
对
For how long?
多久了
Ever since we all met.
那天派对后就开始了
Well, I didn't know...
我并不知道
...who she was, or who you... are, were.
你和她是谁
So...
所以
...you put it together at some point, right?
后来你知道了 对吧
No.
没有
No?
确定
I'm sorry, at some point, I, um...
对不起 后来我是知道了
When?
什么时候知道的
Well, I think...
大概
What? When?
什么时候
When? Umm...
Yeah.
好吧
- Tess, You got your phone? - Yeah.
-泰斯 拿到手机没 -嗯
Okay, why don't we go.
那我们走吧
I'm so sorry.
不好意思
Are you okay? Should I not be here?
你没事吧 我来的不是时候吗
Probably not.
是的
- Oh, I screwed up big time. - What happened?
-这次闯大祸了 -怎么了
Oh, shit!
操蛋啊
Oh, that's my mom.
我妈来了
Hi, Mom.
妈
I'm sorry, do you have a daughter?
'Cause this one's mine.
你没有女儿吧 她是我女儿
-What - Who do you think you are, telling her
-什么啊 -你以为你是谁啊 告诉我女儿
she should have sex with her boyfriend?
需不需要和她男朋友做爱
You know what? What she needs to do is...
她需要的是
No, you shut it!
你住嘴
Dyke.
I didn't tell you about the kitchen remodel.
还没和你说厨房改造的事情
They talked to the guys in
Rome about the travertine.
他们和罗马人谈石灰华
Apparently when they were lifting it up,
it snapped or something so I'm leaving without...
不过他们拿起来的时候断了 我就直接走了
Is your dad here?
你爸在吗
He went to the market.
他去市场了
Sorry to just come over like this,
不好意思 这样冒昧的就来了
but he hasn't been returning my calls, so...
他没有回我电话 所以
I'll tell him you came by.
我会告诉他你来过的
What are you gonna do with that?
你一个人吃的完吗
You want one?
你要吗
Oh, sure.
好
Hi.
You know how many calories are in that?
你知道这块面包多少卡路里吗
I just want to talk.
我们谈谈吧
It really was a coincidence. Okay?
真的是个巧合
And I wanted it to stop.
我想告诉你们来着
But she needed massages and we sort of...
Oh, thank you.
但是她想要按摩 我们
We sort of became friends...
我们成为了朋友
...and I didn't know what to do.
我也慌了
She needed massages?
她需要按摩吗
You knew what to do. You just didn't do it.
你知道该怎么做 你只是不想而已
Well, I was very torn.
我很痛苦
So while you were being torn...
你很痛苦
...she was poisoning our relationship
她在离间我们
and poisoning your perception of me.
说我的坏话
Why would you want that?
为什么这么做
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean...
我想说
Except maybe I was trying to protect
myself, you know, because...
我可能在保护自己
...you know...
你知道的
...because we'd both been
married before, and...
我们都结过婚
...you know how things can turn out.
不了解清楚对方的后果是什么我们都清楚
What about us? What about...
那我们呢
...protecting us?
你有保护我们吗
I didn't protect us.
我没有
And it didn't get poisoned, Albert.
艾伯特 她说的坏话对我没影响
I still really wanted us
to keep seeing each other.
我还是很爱你
I wouldn't know how, you know?
别为难我
I'm so, so, so sorry.
我很抱歉
I know this sounds...
这听起来
...corny...
很俗
...but you broke my heart.
不过你确实伤了我的心
And I'm too old for that shit.
我已经不再年轻了
And the worst part...
最糟糕的是
...the worst part of
it is that you made me
最糟糕的是你让我
look like an idiot in
front of my daughter.
女儿怎么看我
I'm the idiot!
我才是傻瓜
I'm the idiot.
我才是
Look, I got a lot to do.
我很忙
Tess and everything. School
泰斯学校的一些事情
When is she leaving?
她什么时候走
Next week. School starts early for her.
下星期 她学校开学早
Yeah, same for Ellen.
艾伦也是
I guess we have to
get those hobbies going.
该与兴趣相依为命了
Guess so.
是啊
Bye.
拜拜
He just really, really liked you.
他很爱很爱你
I just really, really liked him.
我也是
Computer, What's the point in this?
You do all the thinking where we...
Just digging shelters in the snow
Build a house of dream and domino
I know it's fallen down
Got my headphones on
and I won't hear a sound
No, it's all broke down
Eyes out on the road
but no one comes along
When you want them to
Let your hair hang long
Yeah, that old north
wind is blowing
How will you gonna know which one is your room? Honey.
你怎么知道你的宿舍在哪
It's all written down. And remember, Mom,
可以看到的 我们上次去的时候
we saw everything on our visit.
不是看到了吗
I don't remember anything.
我忘了
- I do. - Ok.
-我没有啦 -好
She's going to be great.
她可以的
You're going to be great.
你可以的
I love you guys.
我爱你们
I love you, too.
我也爱你
Computer, what's the point in this?
You do all the thinking where we...
Just building shelters in the snow
Build a house of dream and domino
I know it's fallen down
Got my headphones on
and I won't hear a sound
Yeah, it's all broke down
Eyes out on the road
but no one comes along
When you want them to
Well, we made a fine person.
我们的好女儿啊
Hey, Eva!
伊娃
Do you think you can help me?
能帮我下吗
Of course! Oh, my God.
当然 天哪
I'm such an idiot! I'm sorry.
我太傻了 对不起
Sorry. Is that... Jeez.
抱歉 那是 天哪
I'm sorry.
抱歉
This thing's heavy.
好重啊
We always go to my mother's
house for Thanksgiving...
感恩节我们都去我妈家过
...and I get in a fight
with my sister and brother.
我兄弟姐妹疯在一起
My sister's a middle child,
so she has issues.
我妹是第二胎 她问题多着呢
Anyway, what are you doing?
你会怎么过
Huh? What are you doing
for the holiday?
你假期怎么过的
I'm going to my friend's house.
我去朋友家
It's going to be a small group, but...
人不多 不过
That sounds nice.
很好啊
Oh, yeah.
呵呵
Hi, honey.
你好
Oh, thank you so much.
谢谢
No problem.
不用谢
It really smells good in here!
太香了吧
Yeah? I can't smell it anymore.
我味觉失灵了
It's unbelievably delicious sound...
Sounding. Smelling.
绝顶美味啊
You excited?
兴奋吗
Oh, my God, beyond!
天哪 无比兴奋
You think she'll look different?
你觉得她变样了吗
Yeah, maybe she grew
a beard or something.
可能长胡子了
You know how it is at Sarah Lawrence.
你知道莎拉·劳伦斯学院的
No, she looks the same.
I Skyped with her yesterday.
我昨天和她视频了
Actually, I think she's gained weight.
她应该变胖了
What time are you picking her up?
什么时候去接她
Not till two.
两点
We're eating at five... you should just
五点开饭 你应该直接从这
come straight here from the airport.
出发去机场
Oh, let's use the fancy plates.
用高档盘子吧
But you say you don't like them.
你不是不喜欢吗
I know. But it's Thanksgiving...
今天是感恩节
you're supposed to use the ugly plates.
就应该用我不喜欢的盘子
Okay, I'll see you. Bye.
待会见 拜拜
- Bye, Eva! - Bye, Cathy.
-拜拜 伊娃 -拜拜 凯茜
Hi.
你好
Oh, wow.
嗯
Okay.
好吧
I don't always park in front of your house.
我很少这样干
I usually just drive by.
我以前直接开过去的
Sometimes I drive by your house, too.
有时候我也会开车经过你家
You do?
是吗
You look good.
你看起来不错啊
You, too.
你也是
Thank you.
谢谢
Is Tess coming home for Thanksgiving?
泰斯回来过感恩节吗
She's already here. She's over at her mother's.
她已经回来了 她去她妈那了
I'm going over there later.
我晚点过去
You want to come?
你想来吗
And Ellen is...
艾伦
This afternoon. She's coming home this afternoon.
艾伦今天下午回来
You been okay without her?
没有她还习惯吗
Oh, sure, yeah.
嗯
I mean, she's not going back.
'Cause I've built a cage.
What a good idea!
好主意
I've missed you.
我想你
I missed you, too.
我也想你
Oh, I should tell you...
I bought some night tables.
我买了床头柜
You did?
真的吗
No.
肯定是假的啊
No, I didn't.
我没有买啦
Okay. That's good.
无所谓啦
I like your toothy smile
It never fails to beguile
Whichever way
the wind is blowing
I like the way this is going
I like to watch TV with you
There's really nothing
That I would rather do
Then maybe we can go to bed
And get up
and do it all again
I like the way your pants fit
And how you stand
and how you sit
Whatever seeds
that you're sowing
I like the way this is going
I don't care about the past
None of it was made to last
It's not who you've known
But who you're knowing
I like the way this is going
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-